Okay,
the eleven can be eleven and fifteen.
Hi,
your name is Caio.
Pleasure I came regarding personal maintenance,
I warned you not only at work,
nor would it be maintenance that it's only this store that's here,
not at the mall or there are two,
there's two,
there's another one right here at the mall,
is it that no has the other?
Could be.
Let me look at who the manager is here.
Kátia Kátia,
she's here.
No,
only Kátia came.
They didn't notify you of the repair.
Not maybe it was there in the other one.
No,
they didn't pass to you in the repair here would be repair.
Of what?
I came here to fix your day.
My name is Caio.
I'm from the Brigadier's workshop.
E
this chocolate ball contains 20g of happiness.
How many congratulations do you need on your day today?
Very, very,
very how much are you?
Three reais a unit.
The unit is Belgian chocolate and we work with milk,
the girl only has chocolate today.
1 box.
I'm still not serious.
I'm so dumb.
Got over marketing.
Very good.
That's it here I'm EU is that it?
You're following,
or following,
Massa is worth it.
Let me leave 1 little box here for you.
Thanks, saw?
Let me pay in profile Guy was found there is CPF.
They love Brigadier.
Thank you,
.
You have 1 great day.
Hope you like everything good bye bye worth bye bye.
Yes.